Finding Aid for the Father James Harold Flye Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series 13 - Photography
  - Photos, 368-376 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 377-389 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 390-401 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 402-411 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 412-421 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 422-431 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 432-443 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 444-454 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 455-465 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 466-474 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 475-483 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 484-497 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 498-511 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 512-522 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 523-534 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 535-545 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 546-555 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 556-565 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 566-577 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 578-587 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 588-597 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 598-607 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 608-620 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 621-629 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 630-639 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 640-648 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 649-658 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 659-670 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 671-683 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 684-694 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 695-705 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 706-716 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 717-727 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 728-737 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 738-747 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 748-757 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 758-767 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 768-777 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 778-786 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 787-796 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 797-806 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 807-814 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 815-824 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 825-834 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 835-844 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 845-852 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 853-862 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 863-872 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 873-882 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 883-892 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 893-908 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 909-918 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 919-928 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 929-938 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 939-946 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 947-958 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 959-970 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 971-982 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 983-994 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 995-1006 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1007-1017 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1018-1027 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1028-1036 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1037-1046 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1047-1056 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1057-1066 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 1067-1077 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1078-1089 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1090-1101 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1102-1112 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1113-1118 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1119-1128 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1129-1137 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1138-1148 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1149 1153 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1154-1166 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1167-1177 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1178-1187 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1188-1197 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1198-1207 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1208-1218 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1219-1229 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 1230-1242 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 1243-1252 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 1253-1262 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1263-1273 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1274-1284 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1285-1297 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1298-1311 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1312-1334 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1335-1344 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 1345-1356 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1357-1365 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1366-1375 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1376-1387 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1388-1397 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1398-1407 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1408-1415 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1416-1427 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1428-1437 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1438-1449 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1450-1460 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1461-1470 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1471-1480 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1481-1490 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1491-1500 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1501-1510 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 1511-1520 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 1521-1530 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 1531-1540 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1541-1550 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1551-1560 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1561-1570 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1571-1580 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1581-1590 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1591-1600 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 1601-1610 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1611-1620 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1621-1630 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1631-1640 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1641-1650 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1651-1660 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1661-1670 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1671-1680 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1681-1690 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1691-1700 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1701-1710 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1711-1720 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1721-1730 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1731-1740 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1741-1750 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1751-1760 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 1761-1770 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 1771-1780 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 1781-1790 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1791-1800 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1801-1810 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1811-1820 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1821-1830 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1831-1840 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1841-1850 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 1851-1860 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1861-1870 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1871-1880 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1881-1890 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1891-1900 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1901-1910 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1911-1920 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1921-1930 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1931-1940 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1941-1950 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1951-1960 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1961-1970 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1971-1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1981-1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1991-2000 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 2001-2010 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 2011-2020 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 2021-2030 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 2031-2040 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 2041-2050 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 2051-2060 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 2061-2070 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 2071-2080 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 2081-2090 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 2091-2100 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 2101-2110 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1981-1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1991-2000 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 2001-2010 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 2011-2020 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 2021-2030 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 2031-2040 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 2041-2050 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 2051-2060 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 2061-2070 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 2071-2080 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 2081-2090 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 2091-2100 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 2101-2110 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 2111-2120 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 2121-2130 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 2131-2140 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 2141-2150 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 2151-2160 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 2161-2170 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 2171-2180 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 2181-2190 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 2191-2200 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1938, 1940; 2201-2210 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1938, 1953, 1965; 2211-2220 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 2221-2230 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 2231-2240 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 2241-2250 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 2251-2260 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 2261-2270 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 2271-2280 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 2281-2290 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 2291-2300 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 2301-2310 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 2311-2320 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 2321-2330 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 2331-2340 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 2341-2350 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 2351-2360 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 2361-2370 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 2371-2380 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 2381-2390 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 2391-2400 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 2401-2410 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 2411-2420 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 2421-2430 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 2431-2440 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 2441-2450 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 2451-2460 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 2461-2470 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 2471-2480 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 2481-2490 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 2491-2500 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 2501-2510 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 2511-2520 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 2521-2530 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 2531-2540 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 2541-2550 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 2551-2560 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 2561-2570 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 2571-2580 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 2581-2590 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 2591-2600 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Photos, 2601-2610 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 2611-2620 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 2621-2630 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 2631-2640 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1947-Paris; 2641-2680 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1947-Paris; 2681-2720 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1947-France and Italy; 2721-2760 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2761-2770 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2771-2780 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2781-2790 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2791-2800 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2801-2810 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2811-2820 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2921-2830 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2831-2840 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2841-2850 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2851-2860 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2861-2870 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2871-2880 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2881-2890 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2891-2900 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2901-2910 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2911-2920 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1940s,1950s-St. Andrew’s School; 2921-2930 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1940s,1950s-St. Andrew’s School; 2931-2940 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2941-2950 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2901-2910 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1947-Italy; 2911-2920 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Photos, 1940s,1950s-St. Andrew’s School; 2921-2930 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1940s,1950s-St. Andrew’s School; 2931-2940 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2941-2950 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2951-2960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2961-2970 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2971-2980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2981-2990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 2991-3000 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Photos, Father Flye; 3001-3010 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Photo album, c. 1910-Lakeland, Florida (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Photo album, 1924-Milwaukee friends (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1952-O’ban festival, New York City; 3011-3020 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1920s,1960s-Order of the Holy Cross; 3021-3030 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Photos, 1920s, 1960s-Order of the Holy Cross; 3031-3040 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1920s, 1960s-Order of the Holy Cross; 3041-3050 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1920s-Order of the Holy Cross; 3051-3060 and memorabilia (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1940s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3061-3070 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1940s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3071-3080 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 1920s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3081-3090 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 1950s, 1960s, 1970s-miscellaneous; 3091-3100 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Photos, 1920s, 1960s, 1970s-miscellaneous; 3101-3110 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Photos, 1940s-Nashville; 3111-3120 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Photos, 1940s-Nahsville, St. Andrew’s School; 3121-3130 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1940-Photo exhibition, Sewanee, TN; 3131-3140 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1940s-New York City; 3141-3150 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Photos 3151-3160 (with correspondence-Jane Fletcher & Evelyn Draper {3}, Dorothea ? {4}, Harvey & Ethel Simmonds {1}, Alexis Levitin {1}, F. Gavin {1} (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1940s-New York City; 3161-3170 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1940s-New York City; 3171-3180 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1940s-New York City; 3181-3190 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 1940s-New York City; 3191-3200 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Photos, 1915-1960s-miscellaneous; 3201-3210 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1950s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3211-3220 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Photos, 1920s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3221-3230 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 1950s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3231-3240 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Photos, 1950s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3241-3250 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Photos, 1910s, 1960s-miscellaneous; 3251-3260 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Photos 3261-3270 (Extra publicity photos of Father Flye) (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Series 14 - Audio Tapes
  - James Agee-The Quiet One, reel 1. 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - James Agee narrating the film he and Helen Levittt made. This is a copy made for Father Flye by Peter Fritsch, brother of Agee’s third wife, Mia.
  - James Agee-The Quiet One, reel 2. 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Bride Comes to Yellow Sky (commentary). 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Side 1. Bride Comes toYellow Sky, followed by commentary
    - Side 2. not full
    - Apparently recorded from television.
  - James Agee to Grace Houghton Flye (Father Flye’s wife) and quotations and poems 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Poems and radio programs about nutrition and alcoholism. 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - James Agee to Grace Houghton Flye. 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - James Agee letter to Mrs. Flye made by Agee for Mrs. Flye’s birthday.
  - Copy of Agee’s letter to Mrs. Flye. 3” tape (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - James Agee reading from his own and others’ poetry. 5” tape (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - James Agee speaking or reading in 1953. 5” tape (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - James Agee reciting and reading. 7” tape (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Selections from Agee in his own voice. 3” tape. Approximately first 75 feet blank. (Box 56, Folder 10a)
  - James Agee, Lincoln, Script I. Television script by Agee. 5” tape (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - James Agee, Lincoln, Script II. 5” tape (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - James Agee, Lincoln script; letter from Mrs.Wittenbach to Father Flye. 5” tape (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - James Agee, Introduction to Lincoln; President Nixon, April 26, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Martha Deane: Interview with Father Flye about James Agee, July 25, 1962. 7” tape (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Interview with Father Flye and Dwight MacDonald, Aug. 5, 1962, for Camera 3 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - The Way to Go, Oct. 13, 1963, Father Flye about James Agee. 5”tape
  - Side 1. re: The Letters of James Agee to Father Flye (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Side 2. Interview with Father Flye for Camera 3, Aug. 5, 1962. 3” tape
  - Father Flye talks at Friends School, N.Y. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Father Flye talks about James Agee. 3 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Letters from Mrs. Wittenbach and to Laura Agee Wright. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - From Father Flye to Mrs. Wright from Omaha, 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Mrs. Wright talking with Father Flye, 1962. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - A Mr. A.L.Agee of Detroit talking with Father Flye in 1963; Aldous Huxley reading Brave New World. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Father Flye speaking of a portrait of James Agee at age 11 painted by Mrs. Flye. 7 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Kesler and Father Flye. 5 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Kesler, then Patty Wallace, on Agee. 5 ‘ tape (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Side 1 Under Milkwood. (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Side 2 Patty Wallace and Father Flye talking about James Agee. 5 “ tape
  - Side 1 David McDowell reading an essay by Robert Penn Warren (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Side 2 Bruce Spang and Father Flye talking about James Agee. 5 “ tape
  - Father Flye and George Moore about James Agee, May 1971. 7 “ tape (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Side 1 Paul Dell and Father Flye talking about James Agee. (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Side 2 Robert Costa talking about Oxford. 7 “ tape
  - Victor Kramer and Father Flye talking about James Agee. 7 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Olaf Hansen and Father Flye. 7 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - St. Barnabas Church, Omaha, Trinity Sunday 1959. Mass, Confirmation, and Sermon. Bishop Brinker. 5 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Sermons, Father Flye, 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Omaha---sermon and talk about the Church by Father Flye, 1959. 7 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Beginning of a talk by Father Flye at a funeral service in 1960. 3 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Two sermons by Father Flye, Aug. 7, 1966 and Aug. 20, 1967. 3 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Sermons by Father Flye, Summer 1967. 5 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Sermon, Aug. 4, 1968. 3 “ tape. (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Sermons, July 1969. 3 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Sermon, Aug. 1969. 3 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Father Flye celebrating a low mass, Aug. 1968. 3 “ tape (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Sermons by Father Flye, 1970. Cassette. (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Sermons, Aug. 1971. Cassette (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Father Flye-sermon. Cassette (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Father Gerald Vann. 7 ‘ tape (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Side 1 Music Side (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - 2 Father Flye ---reading
  - Side 1 Alan Lomax on Voice of Firestone, June 1959 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Side 2 Voice of Firestone. 5 “ tape
  - Father Mathiessen and Father Flye; then Thurber; then Edwin O’Connor. 5 ‘ tape (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Maple Tree. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - “Love Is Blue”; then about the Maple Tree. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Election 1964. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Presidential election, 1968. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Comments on current events, 1968. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - Comments on launching Apollo to the moon, 1969. 3 ‘ tape (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - Side 1 Comments by Father Flye on current events, Nov. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - Side 2 Telephone conversation with Robert Costa. 3 “ tape
  - Comments on campaign and presidential election of 1972. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - Father Flye’s comments on the election of Jimmy Carter, 1976. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 58)
  - Side 1 Greetings from friends (Box 59, Folder 59)
    - Side 2 Father Flye’s thoughts on the class of 1958. 5 “ tape
  - Father Flye---recollections, 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 60)
  - Leaving Omaha, 1959; in New York, 1960-1963. 5 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 61)
  - Abu Latif; French poems. 5 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 62)
  - Dictation, Aug. 1960---New York, Bahamas, Stroops. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 63)
  - Coming to New York, Sept. 1959. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 64)
  - New Year’s Eve, 1961. Recollections, Feb. 1961. Christmas Eve 1962. 5 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 65)
  - Sept. 1961-June 1962. Schools opening and closing. 3 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 66)
  - Comments by Father Flye, 1962, 1965, 1968. 5 “ tape (Box 59, Folder 67)
  - To Senator Gore; Maine, family, Sept. 1965. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 68)
  - Beginning of comment on New Year’s Eve, 1966 and 1967 and statement on difficulty in verbal expression. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 69)
  - Comment by Father Flye about physical state, July 1967. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 70)
  - Father Flye on his physical state, June 1967. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 71)
  - As to anniversaries; mention of Dr. Hanna. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 72)
  - Start of a dictation, 1970. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 73)
  - Father Flye on his physical state; letter to Martha Deane, 1970. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 74)
  - Start of a recording by Father Flye; Leacock College. Cassette (Box 60, Folder 75)
  - Comment on current changes in the Church and St. Luke’s, 1971. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 76)
  - Father Flye’s comments on increasing difficulty in written expression, April 1973. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 77)
  - Father Flye’s comments on his situation and questions about the future, 1973. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 78)
  - Father Flye and Harvey Simmonds, Jan. 1, 1975. Cassette (Box 60, Folder 79)
  - Copy of 79. 79b. Copy of 79. (Box 60, Folder 79a)
  - Beginning of comments, New Year’s, 1977. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 80)
  - Father Flye; Robert Costa, Sept. 1977. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 81)
  - Father Flye on memory, June 1978. 3 “ tape (Box 60, Folder 82)
  - Father Flye on his 95th birthday, Oct. 1979. Cassette (Box 61, Folder 83)
  - Letter from Father Flye to Father Pestina. 3 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 84)
  - Letter to Bishop Claiborne, 1966. 3 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 85)
  - Letter to Lee Graham; taped interview with Lowell Thomas. 3 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 86)
  - Robert Costa. 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 87)
  - Robert Costa and Father Flye. 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 88)
  - Robert Costa, Aug. 1964. 3 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 89)
  - Robert Costa and Charles Gale, Aug. 1968. 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 90)
  - Side 1 Robert Costa and Father Flye (Box 61, Folder 91)
    - Side 2 Robert Lowell reading from his poems, Sept. 1969. 5 “ tape
  - Robert Costa and Father Flye, 1970? 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 92)
  - Robert Costa and Father Flye, April 1970. 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 93)
  - Robert Costa and Father Flye, Jan. 1971. 5 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 94)
  - Side 1 Carleton Fredericks; then Robert Costa and Father Flye (Box 61, Folder 95)
    - Side 2 Martha Deane program, 1972. 5 “ tape
  - Robert Costa, 1971. 7 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 96)
  - Robert Costa, 1971. Cassette (Box 61, Folder 97)
  - Robert Costa and Father Flye, March 1972. 7 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 98)
  - Father Flye and Robert Costa, Dec. 1973. 4 “ tape. (Box 61, Folder 99)
  - Letter to Bishop Hart. 3 “ tape (Box 61, Folder 100)
  - Charles Gale to Father Flye, April 1962. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 101)
  - Selections on death read by Charles Gale, July 1962. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 102)
  - Charles Gale talking to Father Flye and reading Yeats and Frost, 1963. 4 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 103)
  - Letter from Charles Gale, April 1967. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 104)
  - Charles Gale to Father Flye, Feb. 1966. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 105)
  - Charles Gale---music, English selections, Dr. Faustus, Yeats. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 106)
  - John Zeigel to Father Flye, June 1959. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 107)
  - John Zeigel and Father Flye, 1960. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 108)
  - Man Sing Eng. Cassette (Box 62, Folder 109)
  - Man Sing Eng and Father Flye. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 110)
  - Man Sing Eng talking with Father Flye, Sept. 1971. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 111)
  - Dick Needles, May 1964. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 112)
  - Dick Needles, June 1966. 3 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 113)
  - Father Flye and Dick Needles, May 1964. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 114)
  - Alexis Levitin talking with Father Flye, Jan.1972. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 115)
  - Alexis Levitin and Father Flye, 1964. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 116)
  - Scientology, Nathan Hightower; Carleton Fredericks. 5 “ tape (Box 62, Folder 117)